nexonkiller.com 2010-03-29

# Privacy Policy - GameKiller - Maple Story Hacks, Combat Arms Hacks & WonderKing Hacks

_**My Personal Information**_

> We automatically collect the following information:

  * Name of the domain and host from which you access the Internet. 
  * The Internet Protocol or IP address of your computer. 
  * The browser software and operating system you are using. 
  * Your geographic location, the time and date you accessed our site. 
  * The Internet address you visited just prior to visiting our Web site. 

Personal information is also gathered when you sign up on our forums or enter any personal statements in private messages and forum messages. During these instances, our site asks for information such as your nickname, e-mail address, birth date (optional), and other optional information that you may choose to give. We may also ask you for other information at other times. 

_**How is my information used?**_

  * To solve problems such as scams and attacks. 
  * To administer our website. 
  * To help diagnose problems with our services. 
  * To help gather and report aggregate information about the site usage. 
  * Your information is collected through IP log files. 

Our site uses information collected from server log files, such as IP addresses, to help diagnose problems with our services, to administer our Web site, and to report and gather aggregate information about site usage and user demographics. The aggregated data may be shared with advertisers or business partners. Cookies are used to store and sometimes track information about you. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web service and stored on your computer's hard drive. You can set your browser to refuse to accept cookies, but if you do we will not be able to customize the Web site's features according to your preferences. 

_**With whom is my information shared?**_

  * Your information is shared with the appropraite GameKiller.net staff. 
  * Some information is shared with advertisers. (Not including your personal information) 
  * Some of your information is related with GameKiller's related companies. 

When you are on an area of the Web site and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with GameKiller.net and its related companies. If you do not want your data to be shared, you can choose not to allow the transfer by not using that particular service. GameKiller.net may make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to our Web site users. Some of these forums require registration. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. Aggregate information compiled by GameKiller.net may be shared with advertisers and business partners as well as used by GameKiller.net and its related companies. Aggregate information will not be linked to personally identifiable information. 

_**Linked Sites and Related Companies**_

Please be aware that GameKiller.net’s promotional partners, advertisers, sponsors, third-party Internet sites, and content providers accessible through our paper may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. GameKiller.net is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third party parties. Users should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing personally identifiable information through co-sponsored, affiliated or linked sites. **In short form:** These terms only belong to GameKiller.net, we are **NOT** responsible in any way, shape or form of other related websites and or GameKiller's advertisers.
